ACCION International Records MS196
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Communications and External Affairs records, 1950 -- 2012; 1985 -- 2005; MS196.006; 62.7 Linear Feet; 238 Audiovisual Object(s); 365 Digital Object(s)
  - Reprints and publicity, 1960 -- 2011; MS196.006.004; 18.1 Linear Feet; 147 Audiovisual Object(s)
    - CNN Insight Microenterprise Development, 1997-02-04; MS196.006.004.023.00194; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Microcredit Summit Microenterprise Development - Faces of Microcredit, 1997-06-01; MS196.006.004.023.00195; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Microcredit Summit Microenterprise Development - Faces of Microcredit, 1997-06-01; MS196.006.004.023.00196; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - UNCTAD Good News - The Microbanks Project, 1997-01; MS196.006.004.023.00197; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - UNCTAD Micro Bancos En Peru, 1998; MS196.006.004.023.00198; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - UNCTAD Good News - The Commission on Enterprise, Business Facilitation and Development, 1998; MS196.006.004.023.00199; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - To Our Credit Bootstrap Banking in America, 1998-01-01; MS196.006.004.023.00200; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - To Our Credit Bootstrap Banking in America, 1998-01-01; MS196.006.004.023.00201; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - A Preview: To Our Credit Bootstrap Banking in America & To Our Credit Bootstrap Banking and the World, 1998-01-01; MS196.006.004.023.00202; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - ACCION Package from "Economically Finanzas" CNN en Espanol, 1998-08-04; MS196.006.004.023.00203; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - ACCION Package from "Economically Finanzas" CNN en Espanol, 1998-08-04; MS196.006.004.023.00204; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Charitable Givers Group, 1998-10-07; MS196.006.004.023.00205; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - CARE International Spanish PSA Promotional video, 1998 -- 1999; MS196.006.004.023.00206; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - ACCION A Closer Look KOAT ABC/7, 1999-06-15; MS196.006.004.023.00207; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - ACCION New Mexico KOB 4, 1999-07-07 -- 1999-07-08; MS196.006.004.023.00208; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - New Mexico News Client Profile, 1999-07-15; MS196.006.004.023.00209; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - New York Coverage, 2000-01-13; MS196.006.004.023.00210; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - "16 Decisions" Aerial Productions, 2000-02-02; MS196.006.004.023.00211; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Dr. Joy Browne Show Client Prole - Robin Ratcliffe, 2000-04-05; MS196.006.004.023.00212; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Maria CNN en Espanol, 2000-10; MS196.006.004.023.00213; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Tu Opinion Cuenta - Master BNN 3 Boston, 2001-02-13; MS196.006.004.023.00214; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - AmEx Video News Release, 2001-04-17; MS196.006.004.023.00215; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - American Express Small Business Service Community Business Launch, 2001-04-17; MS196.006.004.023.00216; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Mexico BBC Global LOYTN, 2002; MS196.006.004.023.00217; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Centro "ACCION USA", 2002-03-23; MS196.006.004.023.00218; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - CNN Business As Usual, 2002-09-29; MS196.006.004.023.00219; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Serving the Very Poor: Participatory Wealth Ranking and CASHPOR House Index (Microcredit Summit), 2003; MS196.006.004.023.00220; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Newsline, 2003-03-04; MS196.006.004.023.00221; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - "Basil Deli and Market" Local 10 Morning News at 5 WPLG-TV (ABC) Miami, 2004-06-06; MS196.006.004.023.00222; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - "Basil Deli and Market" Local 10 Morning News at 5 WPLG-TV (ABC) Miami, 2004-06-06; MS196.006.004.023.00223; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Celebrity Poker Showndown Show 205 Bravo Delivery, 2004-07-08; MS196.006.004.023.00224; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Maria Otero CNN, 2004-07-29; MS196.006.004.023.00225; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Maria Otero CNN, 2004-07-29; MS196.006.004.023.00226; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - PanAm / Strategic Marketing Charity Donations, 2005-08-09; MS196.006.004.023.00227; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Charitable Giving Fieldwork Boston-Waltham Inc, 2005-08-10; MS196.006.004.023.00228; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Maria Otero CNNE, 2006-12-18; MS196.006.004.023.00229; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Selling Out of Scaling Up? NOW PBS National, 2007-09-21; MS196.006.004.023.00230; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
      DVDs
    - To Our Credit Bootstrap Banking and the World Part 1, 1998; MS196.006.004.023.00231; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Centro ACCION Microempresarial, 2000 -- 2010; MS196.006.004.083.00001 (Box 83)
    - La Sociedad Comunal de Ahorro Y Vivienda, 1960 -- 1961; MS196.006.004.083.00002 (Box 83)
    - ACCION calendar, 2010; MS196.006.004.083.00003 (Box 83)
    - Publicity Acão and São Paulo, 1968 -- 1969; MS196.006.004.083.00007 (Box 83)
      Dismantled binder. News clippings in Portuguese and English
    - Maria Otero in the news, 2003 -- 2009; MS196.002840 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Publications, 1961 -- 2012; MS196.006.005; 9.7 Linear Feet; 91 Audiovisual Object(s)
    This sub-series includes publications created and distributed by ACCION International. These include InSight, Ventures, and the ACCION bulletins. These publications were distributed to interested parties and give updates on the organization's projects, campaigns, successes and needs. This sub-series also contains audiovisual material and photographs. The videocassettes and DVDs are of documentaries and advertisements created by ACCION. In addition to PSAs, advertisements and client profiles, there are also longer films including "Bootstrap Entrepreneurs," "Passport out of Poverty," "Los Informales: The Other Economy," "Washed Away," "Helping Millions Help Themselves," and "Voices from the Field - Three Films about Building Financial Inclusion through Microfinance."
    - ACCION Crisis Communication Plan - draft, 2008; MS196.006.005.023.00041; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - ACCION Calendars, 2010 -- 2012; MS196.006.005.023.00042; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - ACCION Publicity Materials, 1997 -- 2011; MS196.006.005.023.00043; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - ACCION Cards and Direct Mail, 1996 -- 2011; MS196.006.005.023.00044; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - InSight #1-3, 2002; MS196.006.005.023.00045; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - InSight #4, 2003; MS196.006.005.023.00046; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - InSight #5, 2003; MS196.006.005.023.00047; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - InSight #6, 2003; MS196.006.005.023.00048; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - InSight #7-8, 2003; MS196.006.005.023.00049; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - InSight #9-10, 2004; MS196.006.005.023.00050; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - InSight #11-12, 2004; MS196.006.005.023.00051; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - InSight #13, 2005; MS196.006.005.023.00052; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - InSight #14, 2005; MS196.006.005.023.00053; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - InSight #15, 2005; MS196.006.005.023.00054; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - InSight #16, 2006; MS196.006.005.023.00055; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - InSight #17, 2006; MS196.006.005.023.00056; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - InSight #18, 2006; MS196.006.005.023.00057; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - InSight #19, 2006; MS196.006.005.023.00058; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - InSight #20, 2006; MS196.006.005.023.00059; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins 1960s, 1964 -- 1968; MS196.006.005.023.00060; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins 1970s, 1971 -- 1979; MS196.006.005.023.00061; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins, 1980; MS196.006.005.023.00062; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins, 1981; MS196.006.005.023.00063; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins, 1982; MS196.006.005.023.00064; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins, 1983; MS196.006.005.023.00065; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins, 1984; MS196.006.005.023.00066; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins, 1985; MS196.006.005.023.00067; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins, 1986; MS196.006.005.023.00068; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins, 1987; MS196.006.005.023.00069; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins, 1988; MS196.006.005.023.00070; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins, 1989; MS196.006.005.023.00071; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins, 1990; MS196.006.005.023.00072; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins, 1991; MS196.006.005.023.00073; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins, 1992; MS196.006.005.023.00074; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins, 1993; MS196.006.005.023.00075; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins, 1994; MS196.006.005.023.00076; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins, 1995; MS196.006.005.023.00077; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins, 1996; MS196.006.005.023.00078; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Bulletins and Ventures, 1997; MS196.006.005.023.00079; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Ventures, 1998; MS196.006.005.023.00080; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Ventures, 1999; MS196.006.005.023.00081; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Ventures, 2000; MS196.006.005.023.00082; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Ventures, 2001; MS196.006.005.023.00083; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Ventures, 2009 -- 2012; MS196.006.005.023.00084; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 23)
    - Ventures, 2005 -- 2011; MS196.006.005.024.00001; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - The Financial Behavior of Rural Residents - Findings from Five Latin American Countries, 2012; MS196.006.005.024.00002; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Archival Materials Pre- 1990, 1977; MS196.006.005.024.00003; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Various Materials, 1961 -- 1989; MS196.006.005.024.00004; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
      Publicity material from early years.
    - Bulletin North, 2009; MS196.006.005.024.00005; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION International Publicity Handouts, 2010; MS196.006.005.024.00006; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION International Products and Services, 2008; MS196.006.005.024.00007; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION International 50th Anniversary, 2011; MS196.006.005.024.00008; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION International Publicity Materials, 1996 -- 2012; MS196.006.005.024.00009; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION Pamphlets and Brochures, 2011; MS196.006.005.024.00010; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
      The majority of the pamphlets are undated.
    - ACCION Pamphlets and Brochures, 2009; MS196.006.005.024.00011; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION Pamphlets and Brochures, 2006 -- 2012; MS196.006.005.024.00012; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Credit Suisse Partnership, 2008; MS196.006.005.024.00013; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - The Profile of Microfinance in 10 Years: Vision and Characteristics, 2004; MS196.006.005.024.00014; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION International - Executive Summary, 2000 -- 2002; MS196.006.005.024.00015; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION International - Envelope Examples, 2004; MS196.006.005.024.00016; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION Spanish Version (From Old Film Reels), 1961; MS196.006.005.024.00017; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION Spanish Version (From Old Film Reels), 1961; MS196.006.005.024.00018; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION English In Venezuela English Version (From Old Film Reels), 1961; MS196.006.005.024.00019; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION English In Venezuela English Version (From Old Film Reels), 1961; MS196.006.005.024.00020; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Audio Visual Testimonios ADMIC, 1983; MS196.006.005.024.00021; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Audio Visual Testimonios ADMIC, 1983; MS196.006.005.024.00022; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
      Betacam (TM)
    - Los Informales: The Other Economy, 1984; MS196.006.005.024.00023; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Los Informales: The Other Economy, 1984; MS196.006.005.024.00024; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - AITEC, 1985; MS196.006.005.024.00025; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - AITEC, 1985; MS196.006.005.024.00026; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - ADEMI: A Solution for the Present and Future, 1985; MS196.006.005.024.00027; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ADEMI English, 1985; MS196.006.005.024.00028; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - ADMIC Video: "El Negocio De Hacerse Grande", 1985; MS196.006.005.024.00029; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - ADMIC Video: "El Negocio De Hacerse Grande", 1985; MS196.006.005.024.00030; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - ADMIC Video: " The Business of Hope", 1985; MS196.006.005.024.00031; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - ADMIC Audiovisual de Filosofia Ingles y Espanol, 1985-10; MS196.006.005.024.00032; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - Univision "The Message of the Informal Sector" Master Tape, 1985-12-02; MS196.006.005.024.00033; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Univision "The Message of the Informal Sector" Master Tape, 1985-12-02; MS196.006.005.024.00034; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - Public Service Announcement with Richard Montalban, 1986-02-11; MS196.006.005.024.00035; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Public Service Announcement with Richard Montalban, 1986-02-11; MS196.006.005.024.00036; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Public Service Announcement with Richard Montalban, 1986-08-01; MS196.006.005.024.00037; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - "Bridging the Gap" Master, 1987-02-12; MS196.006.005.024.00038; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - "Bridging the Gap", 1987-02-12; MS196.006.005.024.00039; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - "Bridging the Gap", 1987-02-12; MS196.006.005.024.00040; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION International "Passport Out of Poverty", 1987-08-31; MS196.006.005.024.00041; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION International "Passport Out of Poverty", 1987-08-31; MS196.006.005.024.00042; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION International "Passport Out of Poverty" Master, 1987-08-31; MS196.006.005.024.00043; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
      Film reel
      filmstrips
    - ACCION International "Washed Away" PSA, 1987-09-21; MS196.006.005.024.00044; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION International "Washed Away" PSA, 1987-09-21; MS196.006.005.024.00045; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION International "Washed Away" PSA, 1987-09-21; MS196.006.005.024.00046; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
      Third Copy
    - "Bootstrap Entrepreneurs", 1988; MS196.006.005.024.00047; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - "Bootstrap Entrepreneurs", 1988; MS196.006.005.024.00048; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - "Paraguay Stories", 1988; MS196.006.005.024.00049; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - Copia Audiovisual Actuar, 1989; MS196.006.005.024.00050; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - Pub. Documentaire "SOGESOL", 1989; MS196.006.005.024.00051; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Audiovisual Actuar Bogota Propaganda Sancho S.A. Pal. Ingles, 1989; MS196.006.005.024.00052; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Documental Para Microempresarios, 1989; MS196.006.005.024.00053; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Propesa "Oportunidades Para Progresar", 1991; MS196.006.005.024.00054; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Guatemala Documental Para Micro-Empresarios Ingles, 1991; MS196.006.005.024.00055; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Guatemala Documental Para Micro-Empresarios Ingles, 1991; MS196.006.005.024.00056; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Literati Films ACCION, 1992-09-02; MS196.006.005.024.00057; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - Literati Films ACCION, 1992-09-02; MS196.006.005.024.00058; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - ACCION Luis' Spanish v/o, 1992-12-02; MS196.006.005.024.00059; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - Iowa Spanish Client Profile, 1995-06-30; MS196.006.005.024.00060; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Heifer International Project "Legacy for Efrain", 1995-06-30; MS196.006.005.024.00061; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Heifer International Project "The Promise" Advertisement / Client Profile, 1995-06-30; MS196.006.005.024.00062; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Literati Films ACCION New York PSA, 1995; MS196.006.005.024.00063; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION Espanol and English, 1995; MS196.006.005.024.00064; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - ACCION SD Spanish Client Profile / Advertisement, 1996-01-01; MS196.006.005.024.00065; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION English US Client Profile, 1996-02-20; MS196.006.005.024.00066; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION "Voices", 1996-02-20; MS196.006.005.024.00067; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION Luncheon, ACCION Summit, 1996-02-23 -- 1996-02-24; MS196.006.005.024.00068; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Institutional Ingles Y Testimonios, 1996-03-22; MS196.006.005.024.00069; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Bravo ACCION! Master Record Tape 1 of 2, 1996-11-22; MS196.006.005.024.00070; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Bravo ACCION! Master Record Tape 2 of 2, 1996-11-22; MS196.006.005.024.00071; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Microcredit: The Business of Survival ACCION Promo/Short Version, 1997; MS196.006.005.024.00072; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Modulo Proteccion Empresarial, 1997; MS196.006.005.024.00073; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Bolivision Spanish Microenterprise Development, 1997-01-01; MS196.006.005.024.00074; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION English Presidential Microcredit Awards, 1997-01-30; MS196.006.005.024.00075; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION INTERNATIONAL Presidential Awards for Excellence, 1997-02-20; MS196.006.005.024.00076; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Nocturo, 1997-04-24; MS196.006.005.024.00077; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Nocturo Stand Up Toros Ines Sanguinetti and Gustavo Lesgart, 1997; MS196.006.005.024.00078; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - ACCION NY Spanish Client Profile / Advertisement, 1998-01-01; MS196.006.005.024.00079; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION NY Spanish Client Profile / Advertisement, 1998-01-01; MS196.006.005.024.00080; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION NY Spanish Client PSA (in Spanish), 1998; MS196.006.005.024.00081; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION Spanish US Network Leadership Summit, 1998-06-12; MS196.006.005.024.00082; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION Spanish US Network Leadership Summit, 1998-06-13; MS196.006.005.024.00083; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION Chicago "Building Healthy Businesses, Strengthening Communities", 1998; MS196.006.005.024.00084; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION Chicago "Building Healthy Businesses, Strengthening Communities", 1998; MS196.006.005.024.00085; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION TX Spanish Client Profile / Advertisement, 1999-07-29; MS196.006.005.024.00086; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION New Mexico "Fulfilling Your Dreams", 1999; MS196.006.005.024.00087; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Roy Jacobowitz Media Traning, 2000-06; MS196.006.005.024.00088; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - American Express Small Business Services Community Business Launch, 2001-04-17; MS196.006.005.024.00089; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - 40th Anniversary Gala Show, 2001; MS196.006.005.024.00090; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - 40th Anniversary Gala Show, 2001; MS196.006.005.024.00091; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - 40th Anniversary Gala Show, 2001; MS196.006.005.024.00092; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Mensaje del Presidente Vicente Fox, 2002-10-04; MS196.006.005.024.00093; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION New York "Accessing the American Dream", 2003-04-08; MS196.006.005.024.00094; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION New York "Accessing the American Dream", 2003-04-08; MS196.006.005.024.00095; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Strategic Marketing Sense - Donors San Francisco, 2005-08-11; MS196.006.005.024.00096; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Strategic Marketing Sense - Donors San Francisco, 2005-08-11; MS196.006.005.024.00097; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - ACCION "Helping Millions Help Themselves" Launch Celebration, 2006-10-24; MS196.006.005.024.00098; ACCION International (Organization) (Case 24)
    - Small Fortunes Microcredit and the Future of Poverty, 2005; MS196.006.005.024.00099; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Small Fortunes Microcredit and the Future of Poverty, 2005; MS196.006.005.024.00100; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)
    - Stories from the Field Excepts from ACCION's New Documentary - Campaign Launch Event, 2006-10-24; MS196.006.005.024.00101; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 24)